[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Although this author spent much of his life outside his native Ireland, his landmark novels Ulysses and A Portrait of the Artist as a Young Man are set in Dublin.", "correct_answer": "James Joyce", "incorrect_answers": ["James Clavell", "James William Mitchell", "James Munro"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Dinophobia is defined as fear of stories about dinosaurs.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Blimpie\u2019s Best 12-inch Sub on wheat is higher in total calories, carbohydrates, and fats than a McDonalds Big Mac.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "To make this dish you would:  leave your cheese outside covered with loose cheesecloth, allow flies to lay their eggs inside the cheese, the maggots will hatch and then spread it on toast.  Enjoy!", "correct_answer": "Maggot-cheese", "incorrect_answers": ["Blutwurst", "Ricci di mare", "Retsina"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who is the leader of The Film Actors Guild (F.A.G.) that is against Team America in the movie Team America: World Police?", "correct_answer": "Alec Baldwin", "incorrect_answers": ["George Clooney", "Sean Penn", "Matt Damen"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these films does not tell the story of a real life teacher?", "correct_answer": "The Principal", "incorrect_answers": ["Stand and Deliver", "Dangerous Minds", "The Ron Clark Story"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the popular Buzz haircut commonly called in Australia?", "correct_answer": "Crew cut", "incorrect_answers": ["Gl number", "Skinhead", "Semi"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these European countries shares a land border with Sweden?", "correct_answer": "Norway", "incorrect_answers": ["Switzerland", "Denmark", "Lithuania"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Cultural anthropology was one of the two classical divisions of anthropology. What was the other one?", "correct_answer": "Physical Anthropology", "incorrect_answers": ["Urban Anthropology", "Variated Anthropology", "Social Anthropology"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Peter Jackson directed which one of these trilogies?", "correct_answer": "The Lord of the Rings", "incorrect_answers": ["The Terminator", "Indiana Jones", "The Godfather"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Although opponents tried to spread rumors that he was in the KKK, this President completely integrated the U.S. Armed Forces.", "correct_answer": "Truman", "incorrect_answers": ["Andrew Johnson", "Lyndon Johnson", "Hoover"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which one of these persons was not a woman?", "correct_answer": "Anders Zorn", "incorrect_answers": ["George Sand", "George Eliot", "Isak Dinesen"]}]